http://www.qbsol.com/privacy-policy

.
.
.
Document Management
See the value of intelligent document classification and search
Partner News
Discover which new digital tools are transforming the energy industry
See office locations
WellEz On Demand delivers well lifecycle reporting in the cloud
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy was last updated on June 15, 2016 and was last reviewed on April 29, 2019.
Version [1.1]
Quorum Business Solutions, Inc. (“Quorum”, “we” or “us”) is committed to safeguarding your privacy online in accordance with this privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”). Please read the following Privacy Policy to understand how your personally identifiable information collected through your use of our web site located at https://www.qbsol.com/ (the “Website”) will be treated. This Privacy Policy does not cover our use of information collected through any other means.
Policy Modifications
We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy without prior notice from time to time to reflect changes in our business practices. Any changes to this Privacy Policy, including information collected and the use and disclosure of information will be posted here. Following any modification, we will revise the “last updated” date at the top of this Privacy Policy, so be sure to check back periodically for the most current version of our Privacy Policy.
Information Collected
For each visitor to our website, our web server automatically recognizes only the visitor’s internet protocol address, but not the e-mail address. Therefore, we only collect visitors’ domain names, and not the e-mail address of visitors to our website — unless that information is voluntarily submitted in one of the forms on the website.
We collect personal information when you provide it in the course of interacting with the website, as well as other information, as may be collected by Quorum from time to time. At the website, you are able to submit forms and e-mails. In so doing, you may be asked to provide personally identifiable information such as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, or information about your interests and activities.
Some web pages created by Quorum use ‘cookies’, which are small text files that may be placed on your hard disk for record-keeping purposes. It is essentially your identification card, and cannot be executed as code or deliver viruses. It is uniquely yours and can only be read by the server that gave it to you. A cookie’s purpose is to tell the server that you returned to that Web Site page. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user’s computer. Furthermore, a cookie in no way gives us access to your computer. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you’d prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. However, you will not be able to take full advantage of a Web Site if you do so.
If your personal information changes and you wish to update it (such as your address), you may contact our website administrator at info@qbsol.com who will correct, update or remove your personal information as requested.
How the information is used
We may use the information you give us to provide services to you, at your request. We may use it to communicate with you through periodic messages regarding services, events, and other information and notices we believe you may find interesting or useful. Quorum will not send you any unsolicited information, including email regarding any commercial offers or advertisements at any time. We value the relationships we have with our customers and future customers. We may use it for confirmation of registrations or other actions you take on the Web Site, and for related customer service needs. We may use third party service providers in connection with our website and make personal information available to them to the extent necessary for them to provide services to us. We may use and share with others aggregated and/or anonymous information that we have collected based on website usage data or statistical information that we have compiled about our users to analyze the design, functioning, and usage of the website in order to make improvements to the website. We may disclose personal information when required to do so by law or to comply with valid legal process such as a search warrant, subpoena, or court order, if we find that a user’s actions violate our policies, or to protect our rights and property, or to our successors to the relevant portions of our business. We may use this information for any other legitimate business purpose. Except as described in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, rent, swap or otherwise share our mailing lists with unaffiliated third parties. Except as disclosed in this Privacy Policy, Quorum will not otherwise provide personally identifiable information to third parties without your consent.
If you are a registered user, you may alter your user profile in order to remove your name from our e-mail recipient list. If you have simply entered your email address on our homepage, please go to our unsubscribe page or notify us by email at info@qbsol.com with “remove” in the subject header and we will remove your name from our e-mail recipient list.
Security
We maintain physical, electronic and organizational safeguards to ensure all personal information is treated responsibly and in accordance with our Privacy Policy. We also restrict access to this personal information within our organization to those employees who need to know that information. Additionally, we safeguard personal information in accordance with applicable data security regulations. However, while we have measures in place to help prevent unauthorized access and maintain data security, no transmission of data over the Internet is guaranteed to be completely secure and we cannot guarantee the security of any information you provide to us. The website does not encrypt information submitted via web forms over the Internet; these submissions may not be secure. Please consider this fact before sending any personal or confidential information over the Internet by any means.
Links
We provide links to other web sites that we believe you will find useful. Linked sites are not under the control of Quorum, and the privacy practices of these other non-Quorum affiliated sites may differ from those of Quorum. Each site is responsible for its own privacy practices. Links are provided to you as a convenience, and the inclusion of any link does not imply the endorsement of the site by Quorum.
Contact Information
If you have any questions, feel free to contact us or e-mail us at info@qbsol.com.
© 2016 Quorum Business Solutions, Inc. All rights reserved.
